drozfans.com 2017-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Well Buzz

**Last Revised: September 2015**

This site collects and uses personal information from its users and readers in order to improve the content and services we deliver. Our Privacy Policy is intended to help you understand _how_ we collect and use personal information as well as options you may have relative to the collection and use of this information. By accessing or using this site, you hereby accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**General Information**

  * This site is produced and hosted in the United States; if you are in a different country, please be aware that your information will be processed and stored in the United States and that you consent to such processing and storage. Privacy and data protection laws in the United States may not be equivalent to the laws in your country of residence.

  * This site is intended for use by persons 18 years and older. We do not knowingly collect or use any information about children under the age of thirteen.

  * Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time; we will post any changes on this page.

  * This site may contain links to third party websites, including links to sites from which we may earn a small commission on the sale of products. If you use these links to leave our site, please note that we do not have any control over (and are not responsible for) the actions or policies of other websites.

  * If this site become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of our assets, user information, including personal information could be included in the transferred assets.

  * If you require any more information or have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info [at] wellbuzz.com

**Information We Collect**

We or our partners may collect information from users of this site at various points while accessing or using this site, whether via a web browser, a mobile device, a non-browser application, or email. The following is a partial list of information that may be collected:

  * We use third-party advertising and analytics companies to serve ads and collect information when you visit our site. Please read on for additional information with respect to how this site uses cookies, beacons, and pixels. If you would like more information about these types of practices and your options, please click here: <http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>. 

  * Our servers utilize log file records that track data such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks.

  * If you give us your email address, we will add you to our email list and will send you information (such as newsletters or emails from our partners) we believe you will find interesting. You may unsubscribe from our list by following the instructions at the bottom of one of the emails.

**Cookies / Beacons / Pixels**

We or our partners may use cookies, beacons, and pixels to collect information while you are accessing or using this site. Cookies are very small text files stored on your computer when you visit websites in order to personalize content and marketing messages. Beacons and pixels are small graphic images on a site, typically used for monitoring and tracking purposes. The following is a partial list of cookies, web beacons, and pixels that might be used:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve customized ads. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visits to this and/or other sites on the Internet. The DoubleClick cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser.

  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting this site: http://g[oogle.com/ads/preferences](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

  * This site participates in the Google Display Network. As a result, you may see ads from third party vendors and ad networks listed on the following site: https://support.google.com/3pascertification/table/4570113

  * You may visit websites listed in the link above to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you may opt out of some third-party cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting this site: <http://www.aboutads.info/>

  * This site uses Google Analytics to better understand how the site is being used in order to enhance the experience of our readers and other users.

  * You may completely block Google Analytics from collecting information by visiting this page: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

  * This site may use cookies, beacons, and pixels in connection with delivering ads on social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, etc.

  * We participate in a variety of independent advertising networks such as Taboola, Solve Media, Media.net, and GumGum. Please visit the websites of these providers if you wish to opt out of any cookies they may have in use at any given time.
